Menu

    * * * #### Enterprise Level Features
                
        * * #### Explore The Platform
                
    * * * Loaded with enterprise level features, webinar.net equips you to create branded, compelling webinars in a snap!
                
    * * * Get To Know webinar.net
                
            * Have one of our webinar experts walk you through the platform and answer any questions you have.  
                
            * Sometimes, a hands-on approach is the best way to really get a feel for a new platform.  
                
            * Immerse yourself in our self-paced, video demo. Go at your own pace - on your own time.  

Privacy Policy
==============

###### WEBINAR.NET PRIVACY STATEMENT

Your privacy is important to us. This privacy statement explains what personal data webinar.net collects from you, through our interactions with you and through our products, and how we use that data.

Our Privacy Policy explains:

* What information we collect and why we collect it;
* How we use that information; and
* The choices we offer, including how to access and update information.

###### PERSONAL DATA WE COLLECT

webinar.net collects data to operate effectively and provide you the best experiences. You provide most of this data to us directly when you register for webinars and events, or interact with our learning management system. We get some of it by recording how you interact with our ads, for example, using technologies like cookies, and receiving error reports or usage data.

* First Name and Last Name
* Phone Number
* Email Address
* Company
* Personal Photo
* Device Information - such as your hardware, operating version, etc.
* IP Address
* Voluntary data: Information you voluntarily provide to the Site or when you contact us for any reason.

###### HOW WE USE PERSONAL DATA

webinar.net uses the data we collect to operate our business and provide you with use of the products and services we and our business partners offer. This includes using data to improve the products and personalize your experiences. We also may use the data to communicate with you, for example, informing you about updates and product information we and our customers have to offer.

###### DATA SECURITY

[webinar.net](https://webinar.net/) takes reasonable steps to protect the Personal Data from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. Our Company has put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the Personal Data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration or destruction.  
  
All data is accessed via secure connections.  
  
In spite of our efforts to establish a secure environment, you should be aware that no information is completely secure on the internet. Therefore, you should always take the necessary safeguards on your own equipment.

###### SHARING PERSONAL INFORMATION

webinar.net does not share Personal Data with any third parties without legal reasons, such as with your consent or to fulfill a contract. webinar.net stores and processes personal data in secure third party applications for day to day business operations. All third party applications used by webinar.net to store or process personal data are committed to GDPR compliance. For more information, please contact info@webinar.net. We will also share personal information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of webinar.net if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to:

* Meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request;
* Enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations;
* Detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; and/or
* Protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of webinar.net, our users or the public as required or permitted by law.

###### HOW TO ACCESS & CONTROL YOUR PERSONAL DATA

We aim to provide you with access to your personal information. If that information is wrong, we strive to give you ways to update it quickly or to delete it – unless we have to keep that information for legitimate business or legal purposes. You can view or edit your personal data in your account settings. However, if you would like to delete your personal data or your account, you can do so by emailing info@webinar.net. You can also make choices about webinar.net' collection and use of your data. You can always choose whether you wish to receive promotional email from webinar.net. You can also opt out from receiving interest-based advertising from webinar.net by contacting info@webinar.net.

###### CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

Our Site is not directed to children under the age of 16. We do not knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of 16. If we obtain actual knowledge that we have collected personal information about a child under the age of 16, that information will be immediately deleted from our database. If a parent believes that his or her child has submitted personal information to us, he or she can contact us via e-mail. We will promptly delete the information upon learning that it relates to a child under the age of 16. Please note that it is possible some of this information may remain archived in web logs and back-up archives after we delete the information from our active database.

###### COOKIES & SIMILAR TECHNOLOGIES

webinar.net uses cookies (small text files placed on your device) and similar technologies to provide our websites and online services and to help collect data. Cookies allow us, among other things, to:

* Store your preferences and settings;
* Provide interest-based advertising; and
* Analyze how our websites and online services are performing.

We also use web beacons to help deliver cookies and gather usage and performance data. Our websites may include web beacons and cookies from third-party service providers. You have a variety of tools to control cookies, web beacons and similar technologies, including browser controls to block and delete cookies and controls from some third-party analytics service providers to opt out of data collection through web beacons and similar technologies. Your browser and other choices may impact your experiences with our products.

###### Third Party Cookies

In some special cases, we also use cookies provided by trusted third parties.  
This site uses Google Analytics which is one of the most widespread and trusted analytics solutions on the web for helping us to understand how you use the site and ways that we can improve your experience. These cookies may track things such as how long you spend on the site and the pages that you visit so we can continue to produce engaging content. For more information on Google Analytics cookies, see the official Google Analytics page: [Google’s Privacy & Terms site](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites)  
  
Third-party analytics are used to track and measure usage of this site so that we can continue to produce engaging content. These cookies may track things such as how long you spend on the site or pages you visit which helps us to understand how we can improve the site for you. From time to time, we test new features and make subtle changes to the way that the site is delivered. When we are still testing new features, these cookies may be used to ensure that you receive a consistent experience whilst on the site whilst ensuring we understand which optimisations our users appreciate the most.  
  
As we sell products, it's important for us to understand statistics about how many of the visitors to our site actually make a purchase and as such this is the kind of data that these cookies will track. This is important to you as it means that we can accurately make business predictions that allow us to monitor our advertising and product costs to ensure the best possible price.

###### THIRD PARTY PRIVACY STATEMENTS

This Privacy Notice governs use of this internet site. However, if you register for (or attend) an event hosted by webinar.net, your participation may be governed by additional and/or different privacy policies, including privacy polices of an event sponsor who may gather or receive and use your data pursuant to its own policy. Upon registering for an event, you should receive the privacy policies that are applicable to your participation in that event and be asked to agree to them. If you register for an event but do not receive event policy notices, or if you have questions about policies presented, please notify us at info@webinar.net before proceeding.

##### About

Webinar.net is the first online presentation platform fully hosted in the cloud. This architecture allows our customers to reach very large audiences without capacity concerns, and enjoy clear, cost-effective pricing.

##### From The Blog

##### Keep Exploring

##### Stay Connected

Menu

    * * * #### Enterprise Level Features
                
        * * #### Explore The Platform
                
    * * * Loaded with enterprise level features, webinar.net equips you to create branded, compelling webinars in a snap!
                
    * * * Get To Know webinar.net
                
            * Have one of our webinar experts walk you through the platform and answer any questions you have.  
                
            * Sometimes, a hands-on approach is the best way to really get a feel for a new platform.  
                
            * Immerse yourself in our self-paced, video demo. Go at your own pace - on your own time.  

Personal data will be used for personalization of ads. By clicking “Allow All”, you consent to our and our partners’ use of ALL cookies and other technologies to process your personal data to personalize your experience and deliver tailored advertising to you, on and off our sites. However you may visit "Preference" to provide a controlled consent and where you can find our privacy policy. Details can be found within the webinar.net Privacy Policy and the webinar.net Data Collection Consent.

×

### About Cookies

Personal data will be used for personalization of ads. By clicking “Allow All”, you consent to our and our partners’ use of ALL cookies and other technologies to process your personal data to personalize your experience and deliver tailored advertising to you, on and off our sites. However you may visit "Preference" to provide a controlled consent and where you can find our privacy policy. Details can be found within the webinar.net Privacy Policy and the webinar.net Data Collection Consent.

[Allow All](javascript:void(0);) [Disable All](javascript:void(0);)

 Necessary Always Active

Necessary cookies help make a website usable by enabling basic functions like page navigation and access to secure areas of the website. The website cannot function properly without these cookies.

 Preferences

Preference cookies enable a website to remember information that changes the way the website behaves or looks, like your preferred language or the region that you are in.

 Statistics

Statistic cookies help website owners to understand how visitors interact with websites by collecting and reporting information anonymously.

 Marketing

Marketing cookies are used to track visitors across websites. The intention is to display ads that are relevant and engaging for the individual user and thereby more valuable for publishers and third-party advertisers.

 Unclassified

Unclassified cookies are cookies that we are in the process of classifying, together with the providers of individual cookies.

Powered by [](https://seersco.com/) 

Select your region to login:
